<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on kanita Loisy</title>
    <link>https://kani12345.github.io/KanitaBlog/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on kanita Loisy</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://kani12345.github.io/KanitaBlog/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Three AR apps ideas</title>
      <link>https://kani12345.github.io/KanitaBlog/posts/idea_ar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kani12345.github.io/KanitaBlog/posts/idea_ar/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;museum-lense&#34;&gt;&#xA;  Museum Lense&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;heading-link&#34; href=&#34;#museum-lense&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;i class=&#34;fa-solid fa-link&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; title=&#34;Link to heading&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;sr-only&#34;&gt;Link to heading&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;idea&#34;&gt;&#xA;  Idea&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;heading-link&#34; href=&#34;#idea&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;i class=&#34;fa-solid fa-link&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; title=&#34;Link to heading&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;sr-only&#34;&gt;Link to heading&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This AR app would give real-time about the objets and monuments surrounding the users, such as information about a historic building, a famous sculpture, etc. This AR application would function like a real-time information lens, allowing users to point their devices at an object or landmark to receive instant details and context. For example, pointing the app at a historic building could reveal information about its construction, architectural style, historical significance, and even notable events that took place there. Similarly, when used in a museum, users could point their devices at artifacts or artworks to access more detailed information than traditional inscriptions could provide.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Example of an AR application: an information lense</title>
      <link>https://kani12345.github.io/KanitaBlog/posts/ubiquitous-ar/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kani12345.github.io/KanitaBlog/posts/ubiquitous-ar/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In our world where as ubiqitous as smartphones are today, AR applications would be part of our daily lives. Here an example of an application that I think would be amongst the most dowloaded.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It would give real-time about the objets and monuments surrounding the users, such as information about a historic building, a famous sculpture etc. It would be sistematically used in a museum as it would be easier than the inscriptions in a museum and could also provide more complete informations. This AR application would function like a real-time information lens, allowing users to point their devices at an object or landmark to receive instant details and context. For example, pointing the app at a historic building could reveal information about its construction, architectural style, historical significance, and even notable events that took place there. Similarly, when used in a museum, users could point their devices at artifacts or artworks to access more detailed information than traditional inscriptions could provide. This would eliminate the need for large wall plaques or guides, offering users an interactive and immersive learning experience. This AR app would serve as a powerful educational resource. In addition to providing basic information, it could include interactive layers, such as 3D reconstructions of historical events, videos explaining the significance of objects, or audio narrations. Students, tourists, and locals alike could benefit from gaining a deeper understanding of their surroundings.  The app could also allow users to customize their experience based on their interests. For instance, someone interested in architecture could set the app to provide in-depth architectural information when viewing buildings, while a history enthusiast might focus on historical facts and cultural significance.&#xA;This AR application would function like a real-time information lens, allowing users to point their devices at an object or landmark to receive instant details and context. For example, pointing the app at a historic building could reveal information about its construction, architectural style, historical significance, and even notable events that took place there. Similarly, when used in a museum, users could point their devices at artifacts or artworks to access more detailed information than traditional inscriptions could provide. This would eliminate the need for large wall plaques or guides, offering users an interactive and immersive learning experience.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The shape of smartphones </title>
      <link>https://kani12345.github.io/KanitaBlog/posts/smartphones/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kani12345.github.io/KanitaBlog/posts/smartphones/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The shape of smartphones has continusly evolved since their introduction to the market: the blackberry phone is quite different from the last Iphone. This changes were mostly driven by changing user needs and technology improvements. Early smartphones were more compact, often featuring physical keyboards or smaller screens, like the BlackBerry and early iPhone models.&#xA;As technology advanced, screens became larger, bezels shrank, and touch-based interfaces became the absolute norm. This shift in shape was influenced by the desire for a more immersive display experience, prompting manufacturers to design taller and narrower phones that are easier to hold but offer more screen space.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ubiquitus computing</title>
      <link>https://kani12345.github.io/KanitaBlog/posts/ubiquitus_computing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kani12345.github.io/KanitaBlog/posts/ubiquitus_computing/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Mark Weiser’s vision of ubiquitous computing from his paper, The Computer for the 21st Century, imagined a world where computers would be seamlessly integrated into everyday life, effectively disappearing as distinct objects. Ubiquitous computing would make technology an invisible helper that responds intuitively to human needs, embedded in objects throughout our environment rather than as standalone devices.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;are-we-already-living-in-a-world-of-ubiquitous-computing&#34;&gt;&#xA;  Are We Already Living in a World of Ubiquitous Computing?&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;heading-link&#34; href=&#34;#are-we-already-living-in-a-world-of-ubiquitous-computing&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;i class=&#34;fa-solid fa-link&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; title=&#34;Link to heading&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;sr-only&#34;&gt;Link to heading&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In many ways, Weiser’s vision has come to life. We already have smartphones, wearables, and IoT devices that blend into our daily routines, providing real-time information and automating tasks, such as display screens giving information in a mall or subway. Smart homes equipped with devices like Amazon Alexa and Google Nest show how computing has moved from desktops to the physical world around us, monitoring conditions, responding to voice commands, and learning from our preferences. The fact that you cna usse this devices simply by looking at them or giving a vocal command really make them ubiquitous. In workplaces, sensors, RFID tags, and cloud computing contribute to environments where data is constantly collected, processed, and used to enhance efficiency and security. Again, as we are not conscious of all of these processes when they happen, they can be seen as ubiquitous&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Input Devices and Interaction Paradigms: the exemple of the google glass </title>
      <link>https://kani12345.github.io/KanitaBlog/posts/input-devices-and-interaction-paradigms/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kani12345.github.io/KanitaBlog/posts/input-devices-and-interaction-paradigms/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;input-devices-and-interaction-paradigms-why-the-google-glass-faiiled&#34;&gt;&#xA;  Input devices and interaction paradigms: why the google glass faiiled&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;heading-link&#34; href=&#34;#input-devices-and-interaction-paradigms-why-the-google-glass-faiiled&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;i class=&#34;fa-solid fa-link&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; title=&#34;Link to heading&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;sr-only&#34;&gt;Link to heading&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Google Glass is classified as a wearable AR device with a head-mounted display and gesture-based input capabilities. This device was intended to create a seamless experience between the physical and digital worlds, providing hands-free access to information through a small screen above the user’s right eye. Google Glass featured a touch-sensitive frame, voice command input, and a built-in camera, aimed at offering real-time, on-the-go data in an unobtrusive way.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unity game project: Christmas Islands</title>
      <link>https://kani12345.github.io/KanitaBlog/posts/christmas_islands/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kani12345.github.io/KanitaBlog/posts/christmas_islands/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 text-align: center&gt; Unity Game Project: Christmas Islands &lt;/h1&gt;  &#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For my unity class, I had to make a 3D unity game. I chose to do a 3D platformer on the theme of Christmas where the player has to collect all the presents to win. Click &lt;a href=&#34;https://kani12345.github.io/KanitaBlog/KanitaBlog/posts/Final_Game.zip&#34; &gt;here&lt;/a&gt; if you want to download the game and &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/Kani12345/ChristmasIsland&#34;  class=&#34;external-link&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;there&lt;/a&gt; if you want to see the project on github.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;finalised-game&#34;&gt;&#xA;  Finalised game&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;heading-link&#34; href=&#34;#finalised-game&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;i class=&#34;fa-solid fa-link&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; title=&#34;Link to heading&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;sr-only&#34;&gt;Link to heading&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The game is divised in three scenes. Upon lanch, the first scene is the menu.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unity project: space maze, a roll a ball project</title>
      <link>https://kani12345.github.io/KanitaBlog/posts/roll-a-ball/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kani12345.github.io/KanitaBlog/posts/roll-a-ball/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 text-align: center&gt; Space maze, a unity roll a ball project for android &lt;/h1&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For one of my class, I had to implement a &amp;ldquo;roll a ball&amp;rdquo; game: a 3D game destined for Androids where the controller can move around a ball by making it roll.&#xA;I decided to implement it as a maze on the theme of space that the user has to solve while collecting stars collectibles.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;building-the-game&#34;&gt;&#xA;  Building the game&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;heading-link&#34; href=&#34;#building-the-game&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;i class=&#34;fa-solid fa-link&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; title=&#34;Link to heading&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;sr-only&#34;&gt;Link to heading&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;setting-up-the-player&#34;&gt;&#xA;  Setting up the player&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;heading-link&#34; href=&#34;#setting-up-the-player&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;i class=&#34;fa-solid fa-link&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; title=&#34;Link to heading&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;sr-only&#34;&gt;Link to heading&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The player isa planet earth that rolls throughout the galaxy. I used &lt;a href=&#34;https://assetstore.unity.com/packages/3d/environments/sci-fi/planet-earth-free-23399&#34;  class=&#34;external-link&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;this asset&lt;/a&gt;.&#xA;On a computer, the player is controlled through the keybord keys. On a phone, it is controlled by tilting the phone. The script is able to recognize if an android device is used or not to change the input accordingly.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Here is the script that allows to control the player:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gestalt laws misapplications</title>
      <link>https://kani12345.github.io/KanitaBlog/posts/gestalt_laws/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kani12345.github.io/KanitaBlog/posts/gestalt_laws/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;how-gestalt-laws-can-be-misleading-when-misused&#34;&gt;&#xA;  How gestalt laws can be misleading when misused&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;heading-link&#34; href=&#34;#how-gestalt-laws-can-be-misleading-when-misused&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;i class=&#34;fa-solid fa-link&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; title=&#34;Link to heading&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;sr-only&#34;&gt;Link to heading&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-are-gestalt-laws&#34;&gt;&#xA;  What are Gestalt laws?&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;heading-link&#34; href=&#34;#what-are-gestalt-laws&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;i class=&#34;fa-solid fa-link&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; title=&#34;Link to heading&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;sr-only&#34;&gt;Link to heading&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Gestalt laws, also known as Gestalt principles, are a set of rules that describe how humans naturally perceive visual elements as unified wholes rather than isolated parts. These principles are essential for understanding how we interpret and organize visual information.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The main Gestalt laws include:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The ultimate display by Ivan E.Sutherland</title>
      <link>https://kani12345.github.io/KanitaBlog/posts/ultimate-display/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kani12345.github.io/KanitaBlog/posts/ultimate-display/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ivan Sutherland’s “The Ultimate Display” is a visionary work that laid the foundation for modern virtual reality and augmented reality technologies. In his essay, Sutherland imagined a future where computers could simulate real-world experiences so vividly that they would be indistinguishable from reality. He foresaw many ideas that are now integrated into our lives, such as interactive 3D environments, digital simulations, and immersive virtual experiences.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;predictions-that-have-already-come-true&#34;&gt;&#xA;  Predictions That Have Already Come True&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;heading-link&#34; href=&#34;#predictions-that-have-already-come-true&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;i class=&#34;fa-solid fa-link&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; title=&#34;Link to heading&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;sr-only&#34;&gt;Link to heading&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;virtual-reality-and-augmented-reality&#34;&gt;&#xA;  Virtual reality and augmented reality&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;heading-link&#34; href=&#34;#virtual-reality-and-augmented-reality&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;i class=&#34;fa-solid fa-link&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; title=&#34;Link to heading&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;sr-only&#34;&gt;Link to heading&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Sutherland predicted the concept of immersing people in computer-generated environments. Today, VR headsets like Oculus Rift and HTC Vive allow users to explore detailed virtual worlds. Similarly, AR technology, which overlays digital information onto the physical world, is prevalent in applications like Pokémon GO or industrial training software.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Angel Project on Blender</title>
      <link>https://kani12345.github.io/KanitaBlog/posts/angel-blener/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kani12345.github.io/KanitaBlog/posts/angel-blener/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 text-align: center&gt; Making an angel on blender &lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;https://kani12345.github.io/KanitaBlog/KanitaBlog/posts/cover_angel_article.png&#34; alt=&#34;Angel&#34; width=700&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In our blender class, we had to make a 3D object of our liking on blender using the tools we learned in class. I decided to make the biblically accurate angel for aesthetic reasons and also because I thought it involved a lot of blender features: the use of different textures, a complex use of the shadow editor, the use of several transformers (array and path) as well as the animator.&#xA;The textures used are not made by me, I will put them all at the end of the article.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shaowen Bardzell: A Pioneer in Feminist HCI</title>
      <link>https://kani12345.github.io/KanitaBlog/posts/feminist-hci-researcher/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kani12345.github.io/KanitaBlog/posts/feminist-hci-researcher/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;shaowen-bardzell-a-pioneer-in-feminist-hci&#34;&gt;&#xA;  Shaowen Bardzell: A Pioneer in Feminist HCI&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;heading-link&#34; href=&#34;#shaowen-bardzell-a-pioneer-in-feminist-hci&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;i class=&#34;fa-solid fa-link&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; title=&#34;Link to heading&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;sr-only&#34;&gt;Link to heading&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Shaowen Bardzell is a leading scholar in the field of Human-Computer Interaction (HCI), known for her groundbreaking work in integrating feminist theory into technology design. Her research has reshaped the way we think about the intersection of gender, design, and user experience, making her one of the most influential figures in feminist HCI. By advocating for more inclusive and socially conscious approaches to technology, Bardzell has brought attention to the often-overlooked needs of marginalized groups in the design of digital systems.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dark design patterns</title>
      <link>https://kani12345.github.io/KanitaBlog/posts/dark-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kani12345.github.io/KanitaBlog/posts/dark-design/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;dark-design-pattern&#34;&gt;&#xA;  Dark design pattern&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;heading-link&#34; href=&#34;#dark-design-pattern&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;i class=&#34;fa-solid fa-link&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; title=&#34;Link to heading&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;sr-only&#34;&gt;Link to heading&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Dark design, also known as dark patterns, refers to manipulative design techniques used in websites and apps to deceive or coerce users into taking actions they may not want to take. These designs exploit user behavior and psychology, often prioritizing company goals like maximizing profit over user interests. Common dark patterns include making subscription cancellations difficult, tricking users into signing up for services, or using guilt-laden language to influence decisions. While these tactics may boost short-term engagement, they erode user trust and can lead to frustration or dissatisfaction. Ethical design, in contrast, focuses on transparency and respecting user autonomy.&#xA;In this article, we will focus on two dark design patterns: the roach motel and the confirm shaming We will also see how then can be redesigned to be more ethical.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is bad design?</title>
      <link>https://kani12345.github.io/KanitaBlog/posts/bad-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kani12345.github.io/KanitaBlog/posts/bad-design/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;human-computer-interface-how-it-can-be-improved-through-better-affordances&#34;&gt;&#xA;  Human-Computer Interface: how it can be improved through better affordances&amp;quot;&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;heading-link&#34; href=&#34;#human-computer-interface-how-it-can-be-improved-through-better-affordances&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;i class=&#34;fa-solid fa-link&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; title=&#34;Link to heading&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;sr-only&#34;&gt;Link to heading&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;what-is-hci&#34;&gt;&#xA;  What is HCI?&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;heading-link&#34; href=&#34;#what-is-hci&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;i class=&#34;fa-solid fa-link&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; title=&#34;Link to heading&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;sr-only&#34;&gt;Link to heading&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Human-Computer Interaction (HCI) is the study and design of how people interact with computers and digital systems. It focuses on creating user-friendly interfaces that enhance the user experience, considering factors like usability, accessibility, and efficiency. HCI integrates principles from psychology, design, computer science, and ergonomics to understand human behavior and optimize technology for intuitive use. It aims to make technology more accessible and engaging by designing systems that align with users&amp;rsquo; needs and capabilities. Overall, HCI seeks to improve the interaction between humans and machines to ensure technology serves people effectively.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HCI Lab 1 : Setting up a blog</title>
      <link>https://kani12345.github.io/KanitaBlog/posts/lab1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kani12345.github.io/KanitaBlog/posts/lab1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;first-lab-setting-up-this-blog&#34;&gt;&#xA;  First lab: setting up this blog&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;heading-link&#34; href=&#34;#first-lab-setting-up-this-blog&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;i class=&#34;fa-solid fa-link&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; title=&#34;Link to heading&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;sr-only&#34;&gt;Link to heading&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Hi there, I&amp;rsquo;m Kanita Loisy, a computer science student pursuing a master degree in virtual and augmented reality. For this master, we have a Human-Computer Interface (HCI) module. For the first lab of this module I&amp;rsquo;ll be setting up this blog.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;setting-up-the-blog-locally&#34;&gt;&#xA;  Setting up the blog locally&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;heading-link&#34; href=&#34;#setting-up-the-blog-locally&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;i class=&#34;fa-solid fa-link&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; title=&#34;Link to heading&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;sr-only&#34;&gt;Link to heading&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;hugo-brief-description&#34;&gt;&#xA;  Hugo brief description&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;heading-link&#34; href=&#34;#hugo-brief-description&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;i class=&#34;fa-solid fa-link&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; title=&#34;Link to heading&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;sr-only&#34;&gt;Link to heading&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Hugo is a fast, open-source static site generator designed for building websites quickly. Written in Go, it takes content in Markdown files and templates to generate static HTML files, making it ideal for blogs, documentation, and portfolios. Hugo supports extensive customization through themes, templates, and configurations, and it allows for easy deployment to various platforms, including GitHub Pages and Netlify. With its speed and flexibility, Hugo is popular among developers and content creators who want a lightweight, scalable website solution.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
